I'm so hungry, Shido!
Shido, potty.
Darling! Darling!
U-Um, Shido?
--Shido! I wanna eat kinako bread!
--Darling, my tummy hurts!
Kaguya! Isn't that my candy?!
Hmph! Don't sweat it!
If you fuss over the small stuff,
it only proves how small-minded you are.
Agreement. You can part with one or two.
--Hey! Stop eating my snacks already!
--Why won't you let me eat one?!
--All right! Everyone just
calm down for a second!
--Hey! Stop eating my snacks already! --Why won't you let me eat one?!
--Darling! Why won't you listen to me?!
--Do that again and I'm gonna tell Shido!
Natsumi... Why have you done this?
You've got it rough, Shin.
Reine!
I'm sorry.
I can't keep up all on my own.
No, I'm the one who's sorry
for leaving them all in your care.
That's so cute.
Um...
What happened to Natsumi?
I deployed observation devices
to find her, but no response yet.
I'll let you know if that changes.
All right.
But, why would Natsumi
do something like this?
I wonder...
It could have been emergency
measures she used to escape.
But by hindering the
Spirit's ability to fight,
perhaps this is her issuing
you a warning as well.
Otherwise, it could be a grudge against you.
As far as we've confirmed,
there are six Spirits gathered
around Shido Itsuka.
As soon as you're ready, I'll have
you make your move, Ellen.
Yes, sir. Who shall I start with?
This is the Spirit from the
AST's report the other day...
She appeared near Tengu City,
and since she hasn't been
confirmed Lost yet,
she's our priority target.
A grand opening amidst the mayhem.
"My Own Personal Zoo."
Now, Shido is tested as a father figure.
"Episode Four:
'Transformation'"
--No way!
--Really!
That's so lame!
I guess everyone here was spared by Natsumi.
Morning, Itsuka.
Y-Yeah.
What's up?
Uh, no! It's nothing!
Um, Itsuka?
Yeah?
Some guests have come
here to see you, but...
Guests?
About that...
I knew you were here, Shido!
I thought I told you to behave
and stay put in the staff room!
Hmm, what have we here?
Bother. You're holding us up.
Shido, do you copy? It's an emergency.
Tohka and the others are
gone from the house!
Yeah, they came here...
Shido, you need to have a talk
with the Class 2-3 teacher!
They don't believe that we're Yamai!
Sigh. These adults can only judge
things by external appearance.
I thought I told you guys
to wait at home.
How come? Isn't it a school day?
That's true, but...
--Hey, you...
--What's your name?
I'm Chiyogami Itsuka.
Thanks for being friends with Papa.
P-Papa?!
No! It's a misunderstanding!
These girls are um... my relative's kids!
I'm just taking care of them!
Papa is only, um...
It's their nickname for me!
I-I see... It being you,
I almost believed they were yours.
Of course they aren't.
Come on, let's all go home, everyone!
What was that just now?
What's wrong, Toh--
Wh-What have you done to me, Shido?!
Bastard! What did you just do?!
--Eh?!
--You're the worst!
That's so lame!
I-I didn't do...
That light...! Don't tell me...!
C'mon, let's go home!
Ugh, he's fleeing!
Shido!
What's up?!
The house!
The house? What about the house?!
"Lucky"
This is...
She's done it now...
Now then, how should I play with them next?
You intend to do nothing after
what Westcott did to us?!
I don't know what to tell you...
What happened makes one thing clear.
He's on a whole different level.
We were foolish to go against him.
Even so, he deserves every ounce
of just retribution we serve him.
Retribution, huh?
What are you suggesting we do?
Right now, Westcott is in
Japan as we speak, correct?
And what of it?
"Stop"
I'm home...
Shido! Shido!
There's so much cake...
Shido! Shido! Are you okay, Shido?
These past few days have been
one thing after another...
Not again!
"My Own Personal Zoo"
What's with this outfit?!
Shin, do you copy?
Reine!
She's gone all out this time.
But thanks to that, I've tracked
down a reaction from Natsumi.
For real?! Where is she?!
You look so silly! Serves you right...
It's your own fault for embarrassing me.
Next is to...
Someone's coming this way.
A friend of Shido's, maybe?
Too bad, you won't be
catching me this time.
For being one of Shido's friends,
that was sure an impactful greeting.
Sorry to disappoint, but I'm not
quite one of Shido's friends.
Then perhaps you're with the AST?
Not that it matters to me...
What do you want?
I've come to hunt you down.
Hmm? I think you'll find that difficult.
We'll only know for sure once I try.
You're only this confident
because... of them?
No...
Well, it makes no difference to me, right?
You little...!
Haniel!
My, my! Thanks for giving
me so many goodies!
Now to return the favor!
Ellen!
Sh-She's...
I must say, you're cuter this way.
What can you do to me now?
This fight isn't over just yet.
This is more than enough to kill you.
No way! What the hell is this?!
I must have missed your vitals.
But your power is falling rapidly.
Now then...
H-Help... No... Help me... No... Help...
Don't worry, it'll soon be over.
What?
You all right?
Wh-Why are you...?
Gabriel, Rondo!
How weak! How weak!
Sneer. How pathetic.
Why...?
Natsumi!
Shido?
Are you okay? We'll patch you up in no time!
You think I'll let that happen?
You might wanna think twice, Ellen.
Your friends are running short.
You're outnumbered.
That doesn't bother me.
Those girls never mattered from the start.
Really? In that case...
Miku!
Now, Kotori!
Hang in there a bit longer, Natsumi!
Why? But why?
A useful pawn would come in handy...
Mr. Simpson...
Right now, at this very moment,
do you know how many DEM satellites
are in geosynchronous orbit?
No...
The answer is 23.
Of these, I'm told eight
are awaiting disposal.
Hold on a minute.
Where are you going with this?
What does that have to do with...
Oh, Murdoch!
You're not thinking of...?!
That's right. Let's dispose of them.
We'll take those junk satellites...
and drop them on Tengu City.
Yes?
Punishment? Mine?
What do you mean?
All this for my punishment?
What's going on here?
That was quick, Shido.
Is it true?! Natsumi woke up?!
Just a bit ago.
Natsumi...
She took enough damage from Ellen
that she can't use her Angel, but...
You should still be careful.
Right.
What happened to your face?
Uh, well... Be on your guard.
Eh? Uh, okay...
Yo, Natsumi.
Hey! Watch it, Natsumi!
Don't look at me!
C'mon, don't say that.
Why did you come and rescue me?
Why? Because Ellen had you beat...
That's not what I mean!
I-I impersonated you and
erased all your friends!
I don't know what to tell you...
When we came across you like that,
of course we'd help.
That's bullshit! Don't think you
can fool me with smooth talk!
That's not my intention, but...
Hey, Natsumi?
What?
Why did you impersonate me
and erase my friends?
Because, you saw and know
my secret, obviously.
Your secret, meaning?
Th-That this is... my true form.
Hold on a sec. Why does being
seen in that form set you off?
Why, you ask?!
Wh-When I'm this much of a disgraceful
mess, how could I not be mad?!
Natsumi, um--
The first time that we met,
you said that I was pretty!
Would you have had the same
reaction if I was like this?!
You probably would've ignored
me even if I talked to you!
I wouldn't--
You would've!
Everyone's the same!
When I'm like this, nobody
ever pays attention to me!
In any case, I'll never forgive
anyone who knows my true form!
That means you, so get lost!
But, Natsumi...
What's so disappointing
about the current you?
That's why I told you to be careful.
How's Natsumi's mental state?
It's been up and down, but sealing her
is out of the question for now.
Figured as much.
Natsumi just doesn't have any
confidence in her current self.
Otherwise, she wouldn't
be transforming like that.
You know, I think the real
Natsumi has a charm of her own.
If only she realized that, too.
She'd rather transform than
show her true self, so...
Transform?
But, Natsumi...
What's so disappointing
about the current you?
Who would... be fooled... by that?!
Once I can finally use Haniel again,
I'm done with this!
What? What the--
Captured!
Yay!
Let me go!
Okay, we're good.
What? Where am I?
Hi! It's a one-day special beauty salon!
Welcome to Salon de Miku!
Huh? What is this?
What is it? Miku just told you.
A beauty salon.
Hold on, I don't get it!
You're just doing this to make me think
I'm pretty but laugh behind my--
Whatever, just lie down already.
You're holding up the schedule.
Schedule?
Natsumi...
For the rest of today, we'll try to
make you transform as best we can.
If we succeed, it's our win.
If there's no difference, we lose.
Then you can do as you please.
What do you mean, do as I please?
Let's see...
What if we let you run away
to wherever you want?
Fine.
It's about time you learn...
...that even without an Angel,
girls can still transform.
We'll start by oiling your skin.
This won't change a...
Now we'll warm up your body
with hot stones. How is it?
It's all right.
This will help the swelling in your legs too.
Oh... R-Really?
Does it feel good?
You ought to be taking much
better care of your skin.
Doesn't matter what I do, it won't...
You fell fast asleep.
Move along to the next room.
Uh, right.
Trust in our skill and behold our work!
For beauty, clothes are where it's at!
Come, this way.
Step on in!
Oh, that's nice!
It's very cute.
Try on this next!
That brings us here to the
final room of your transformation!
I'm Shiori. I'll be using
makeup to transform you!
--That won't change a thing!
--Do you really believe that?
Of course I do!
What if I told you...
...that I'm really a man?!
Pervert.
Ah, look how hurt he is.
Don't worry about it!
If you omit the part about Darling
being a guy, he's still a girl!
Anyways!
I'll use my skills and technique that
even you couldn't see through...
...to show how I can transform you!
Do whatever you want.
All done!
How is it, Natsumi?
This is... me?
What? What's going on here?
Wait, why do they all look so happy?
I did those terrible things...
Losing if I'm cute means I think
I just lost! Because, I'm...
Hey! Natsumi! That way is...
Natsumi!
Natsumi! Are you okay, Natsumi?!
Who is this?
My name is Ellen Mathers.
Have I reached Master Sergeant Tobiichi?
Ellen Mathers...
What is this about?
Let me get straight to the point.
Master Sergeant Tobiichi.
Will you work under me?
I refuse.
I'm not aiding an organization
that brings any harm to Shido.
There she is! This way!
Looks like you're in quite the predicament.
Five years ago, there was
a certain fire in Tengu City...
If you do decide to work under me...
...that information could be released to you.
You want to avenge your parents, don't you?
All right.
This is...
I welcome you... to DEM Industries.
"Episode Five:
'Despair Comes Crashing Down'"